(Howard:)Thank you.
(Stuart:)If you're hungry you can eat
your takeout; nobody touched it.
(Penny:)I think I'm gonna
go for a run.
(Penny:)You want to come?
(Leonard:)No, last time that old lady
in the park kept screaming,
"Watch out, he's
right behind you."
(Leonard:)Hello?
(Strange old man:)Hey, how you doing?
(Leonard:)Uh, can I help you?
(Penny:)I don't think so,
but you're sweet for asking.
What-What are you doing
(Penny:)in our apartment?
(Strange old man:)Oh, I rented a room from
your neighbor, the tall guy...
(Strange old man:)dressed like a little boy.
(Leonard:)Unbelievable.
(Leonard:)Okay, uh, I don't know
what he told you,
(Leonard:)but you can't stay here.
(Sheldon:)So, there are fresh linens
on the bed and...
(Sheldon:)Oh.
(Sheldon:)Well, now, I see
you've met Theodore.
(Sheldon:)Theodore, these
are your new roommates,
(Sheldon:)Leonard and Penny.
(Sheldon:)They're very honest,